http://www.gokulinternational.com/terms-and-conditions/

Track order
Cart
{( mc.cartProds.total_items )}
Hi {( mc.enduser.firstname )}!
Profile
Store Credit
:
Subscription : ( Inactive )
Terms and Conditions
1. Terms By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.2. Use Licensea. Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Gokulinternational.com web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:i. modify or copy the materials;ii. use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);iii. attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Gokulinternational.com web site;iv. remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; orv. transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.b. This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Gokulinternational.com at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format. 3. Disclaimera. The materials on Gokulinternational.com web site are provided "as is". Gokulinternational.com makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchant ability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Gokulinternational.com does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.4. LimitationsIn no event shall Gokulinternational.com or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Gokulinternational.com Internet site, even if Gokulinternational.com or a Gokulinternational.com authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.5. Revisions and ErrataThe materials appearing on Gokulinternational.com web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Gokulinternational.com does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Gokulinternational.com may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Gokulinternational.com does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.6. LinksGokulinternational.com has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Gokulinternational.com of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user's own risk.7. Site Terms of Use ModificationsGokulinternational.com may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.8. Governing LawAny claim relating to Gokulinternational.com web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of British Columbia without regard to its conflict of law provisions.General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site.Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.• Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.• We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.• We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.• We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.• Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.• We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.• We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Back
Search Results:
Sorry!! No such products exist.
Could not find what you looking for? Let us know
Thank you! We will revert to you as soon as possible.
*Name:
*Email:
Contact:
*Message:
Submit
Search Results:
Sold Out
{( ((product.p-product.dp)/product.p)*100 | convert_to_number:0 )}% OFF
Quick Look
Show more
×
Shopping Cart ()
Product Details
Quantity
Price / Item
Total Price
{( cartProduct.title )}
{( cartProduct.option1_value )}
{( cartProduct.option2_value )}
{( cartProduct.option3_value )}
{( prodOption.option.name )} :
{( prodOption.value )}
Uploaded file
{( prodOption.value.text )}
{( optionVal.text )}
Uploaded file
{( '(' + mc.activeCurrencyData.currency + ' ' + prodOption.option.charges + ')' )}
Note:
Price has changed!
This variant is not available anymore.
This product is not available.
Selected product options are not available.
This product is not available.
Product option is not available.
This option value is not available.
This item is invalid.
Price
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( cartProduct.final_price | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( cartProduct.ws_discounted_price | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
{( '(' + cartProduct.ws_discount_percent + ')%' )} OFF
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( cc.cartProds.total_price | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
Minimum order quantity : {( cartProduct.moq )}
{( cartProduct.title )}
{( cartProduct.option1 )} : {(cartProduct.option1_value)}
{( cartProduct.option2 )} : {(cartProduct.option2_value)}
{( cartProduct.option3 )} : {(cartProduct.option3_value)}
{( cartProduct.option1 )} :
{( cartProduct.option2 )} :
{( cartProduct.option3 )} :
{( prodOption.option.name )} :
{( prodOption.value )}
Uploaded file
+ {( prodOption.value.split(',').length - 3 )} more
{( prodOption.value.text )}
{( optionVal.text )}
Uploaded file
{( '(' + mc.activeCurrencyData.currency + ' ' + prodOption.option.charges + ')' )}
Add to wishlist
Add to wishlist
Remove
Note:
Price has changed!
This variant is not available anymore.
This product is not available.
Selected product options are not available.
This product is not available.
Product option is not available.
This option value is not available.
This item is invalid.
Qty
Avail {( cartProduct.ws_nearest_discount.discount_percent )}% OFF on buying {( cartProduct.ws_nearest_discount.quantity )} items.
Price
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( cartProduct.price | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( cartProduct.final_price | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( cartProduct.ws_discounted_price | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
{( '(' + cartProduct.ws_discount_percent + ')%' )} OFF
You save {( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( (cartProduct.final_price - cartProduct.ws_discounted_price) | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
You save {( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( (cartProduct.price - cartProduct.final_price) | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
Total Price
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( (cartProduct.final_price * cartProduct.quantity) | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( (cartProduct.ws_discounted_price * cartProduct.quantity) | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
You save {( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( (cartProduct.final_price - cartProduct.ws_discounted_price) * cartProduct.quantity | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
You save {( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( (cartProduct.price - cartProduct.final_price) * cartProduct.quantity | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
Please enter a positive integer.
Minimum order quantity : {( cartProduct.moq )}.
Minimum order quantity : {( cartProduct.moq )}
There are no items in your cart.
Continue shopping
Congratulations! You have further availed {( mc.cartProds.ws_breakup.storelevel.discount_percent )}% OFF.
{( mc.cartProds.promo.promo_code )}
Subtotal:
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( mc.cartProds.total_price | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
Wholesale Discount:
(-) {( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( mc.cartProds.ws_breakup.total_discount | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
Promo Discount:
(-) {( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( mc.cartProds.promo.discount | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
Total:
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( mc.cartProds.ws_breakup.discounted_price | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( mc.cartProds.discounted_total_price | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( mc.cartProds.total_price | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( mc.productData.activeItem.p | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
{( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( mc.productData.activeItem.dp | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )}
{( ((mc.productData.activeItem.p-mc.productData.activeItem.dp)/mc.productData.activeItem.p)*100 | number:0 )}% OFF
{( option.name )}
{( value.value )} {( value )}
This combination is not available.
{( option.option.name )}
(Extra Charges {( mc.activeCurrencyData.currency )} {( option.charges | convert_price:mc.activeCurrencyData )} )
{( mc.storeinfo.store_type == 'shoppingstore' ? 'Buy Now' : 'Enquire Now' )}
Select Subscription :
{( subscription.name )}
Have a referral code?
Code
*By signing up you agree to our T&C
Sign Up
Signup to Gokul Herbal Infusions
Use your social media account:
Continue with Facebook
Continue with Google
or
Already a user?
A confirmation mail has been sent to {( eac.registerData.email )}. Kindly click on the link to proceed further.
×
Email:
Password:
Log in
Forgot password ?
New to Gokul Herbal Infusions ?
Login to Gokul Herbal Infusions
Use your social media account:
*Reset password link will be sent to your email.
Submit
Please confirm you email id
Please click on the verification link sent through email on {( mc.enduser.email )}
Submit
Copyright @
gokulinternational.com
{( mc.currentYear )}. All rights reserved.
Get your own online store at
Request Callback
Valid
Thank You.
We will contact you soon.
Loading...
For Overseas Orders Contact Us At sales@gokulinternational.com
( Shipping charges will be different for international orders)
